(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-09-08T02:26:01.917736",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.7-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Hey, everybody!
Today, I would like to introduce you
to the one and only entertainer!
Ready...
Go!
始まった show time 鳴り響く歓声
Showtime has begun, cheers echoing all around!
Let's get up, get up, get up
Oh ジャンガジャンガ 心躍らせ
Oh, janga janga, making our hearts dance
Let's get up, get up, get up
指を鳴らせば 変わる景色が
Snap your fingers, and the scenery changes
退屈な街でも ほら ブロードウェイ
Even a boring street turns into Broadway, see?
今宵の主役は私よ
Tonight's leading star is me!
1, 2, let's go, 3, 4!
It's my show time!
It's my showtime!
Let the show begin 最高のショー 楽しみましょう！
Let the show begin, let's enjoy the best show!
一度きりの人生なの ダーリン ダーリン ダーリン yeah
You only get one life, darling, darling, darling, yeah!
恋も仕事も いざ 東雲よ
Romance and work alike, on towards the daybreak!
1, 2, 3, 4, hah!
Let the show begin
照らす moon light スポットライトにして
Turn the shining moonlight into our spotlight
Let's get up, get up, get up
踊ったラタタ 軽快なステップで
Dancing rat-tat-tat with lively steps
Let's get up, get up, get up
音を鳴らせば 拍手の渦が
When the music plays, a storm of applause
轟くスタンディングオベーション
Roars into a standing ovation!
今宵の主役に貴方も
You too can be tonight's star!
1, 2, let's go, 3, 4!
It's our show time!
It's our showtime!
Let the show begin 最高のショー 楽しみましょう！
Let the show begin, let's enjoy the best show!
一度きりの人生なの ダーリン ダーリン ダーリン yeah
You only get one life, darling, darling, darling, yeah!
恋も仕事も いざ 東雲よ
Romance and work alike, on towards the daybreak!
1, 2, 3, 4, hah!
Let the show begin
Come on, trombone!
Do it naughty, everybody come follow me, yeah!
Be scandalous 今にも
Be scandalous, at any moment
Let's get up, get up, get up
Let's do it very, very, very bad
So beautiful
何度でも
Again and again
熱を奪って Very very very bad
Stealing away the heat, very, very, very bad
Let the show begin あなたも燃え尽きましょう
Let the show begin, let's burn ourselves out together
一度きりの人生でしょ Darling Darling Darling yeah
It's a once-in-a-lifetime life, darling, darling, darling, yeah!
恋も仕事もいいね 私のために
Love and work are both fine, all for my sake
One two three four ha!
Let the show begin
Let the show begin 最高のショー 楽しみましょう
Let the show begin, let's enjoy the ultimate show
一度きりの人生なんだ Darling Darling Darling yeah
It's a once-in-a-lifetime life, darling, darling, darling, yeah!
恋も仕事もいいね 私のために
Love and work are both fine, all for my sake
One two three four ha!
This is my show time...
Mwah!
Breaking out Wannabe 他の誰でもないの me
Breaking out, wannabe, it's no one else but me
君の願いも簡単に叶えたいから look at me
I want to make your wishes come true easily, so look at me
Ladies, please understand 嘘だらけの世界とは break up
Ladies, please understand, break up with this world full of lies
Break up! I wish 伸びた ありのままで超えてく future
Break up! I wish, breaking into the future just as I am
見つめるほど ありのまま adrenaline
The more you look, adrenaline flows as it is
Please understand 間違わない adrenalize
Please understand, making no mistakes, adrenalize
こだわる my style 幾度の night 超えてく my guidance
Sticking to my style, surpassing countless nights, my guidance
Now change into my life 見せるだけ 振り向かない I
Now change into my life, I'll just show you, I won't look back
見せてよ luxury
Show me luxury
魅せてよ さらけ出す思いを
Captivate me with feelings laid bare
見せつける ecstasy
Showing off ecstasy
Don't be afraid, I don't care だから don't run away
Don't be afraid, I don't care, so don't run away
Show me without a filter
Be naked, be naked, be naked
手の望むまま girl, be naked, be naked, be naked
Just as your heart desires, girl, be naked, be naked, be naked
Show me without a filter
Do you understand?
Lip on neck, be mostly 手の望むまま girl
Lip on neck, be mostly, just as your heart desires, girl
Lonely more lies, me and my girls yeah
Lip on neck あのステージ だから遠慮はしない
Lip on neck, that stage, so I won't hold back
手がかりにハンド 走り出せ Lambo
Hand as a clue, drive out like a Lambo
惑わせるファンタジー
A bewitching fantasy
魅せてよ 騙されはしないの
Captivate me, I won't be deceived
幕は開ける finally
The curtain rises finally
Are you okay? I'm okay だから don't be afraid
Are you okay? I'm okay, so don't be afraid
Show me without a filter
Be naked, be naked, be naked
手の望むまま girl, be naked, be naked, be naked
Just as your heart desires, girl, be naked, be naked, be naked
Show me without a filter
自分隠すのは楽だよね
It's easy to hide who you really are, isn't it?
周りに合わせてればそれで とりあえず
If you just blend in with everyone,
一人にならずに済むから... くだらないの
at least you won't end up alone... How ridiculous!
本当はもう気づいてて 惑わせ 深層に疼いてる
In truth, you've already noticed, throbbing deep down in your core
なのに何で諦めてる もう一度確かめて
So why are you giving up? Check it one more time
始めましょう リアルな show どこからでも好きにどうぞ
Let's begin the real show, feel free to join from wherever you like
大胆に 派手に show me without a filter
Boldly and flashily, show me without a filter
Hey, what you want? Tell me, please don't be shy
Hey, 夢中に 大丈夫さ
Hey, lose yourself in it, it's going to be alright
Hey, what you want? Tell me, please don't be shy
そのままで girl, yeah it's true
Just as you are, girl, yeah it's true
Hey, what you want? Tell me, please don't be shy
Hey, 夢中に 大丈夫さ
Hey, lose yourself in it, it's going to be alright
Hey, what you want? Tell me, please don't be shy
そのままで girl, yeah it's true
Just as you are, girl, yeah it's true
許さない
Unforgivable.
ぞっとした顔が可愛いね
Your terrified face is so cute.
君のその身体が欲しいの
I want that body of yours.
Love it 何？ What is 愛？ はい
Love it? What? What is love? Yes.
可哀想ね 君は悪い子なの？
How pitiful. Are you a bad kid?
どの子がお好き？ で、無残に
Which girl do you like? And so mercilessly,
色目がお上手で 誑かし
you're good at making eyes and deceiving.
君に踊らされちゃって
Danced around by you,
あたしは狂う
I'm going crazy.
What is Love it?
君の亡骸で 骨の髄まで
With your remains, to the marrow of your bones,
入れて空っぽになる 愛のパペット
filling them until empty, a puppet of love.
胸が苦しいね 息が詰まるのね
Your chest hurts, doesn't it? You're suffocating, right?
それが恋と教えてあげる Ah-ha-ha
I'll teach you that's what love is, ah-ha-ha.
後ろの正面で ほら囁いて
Right behind you, look, whispering,
イイコネ 首輪つけた君はLove it
"Good boy," wearing a collar, you're love it.
イカレちゃったのね 恋は盲目で
You've gone insane, love is blind.
死体にしてあげるわ 逝って Ah-ha-ha
I'll turn you into a corpse, pass on, ah-ha-ha.
濡れた君の赤い生気 溺れるまで
Until drowning in your wet red vitality,
大体のトんで行け 死に恥まで
just fly away, until your shameful death.
愚かね 愚かね 間抜けな顔して
How foolish, how foolish, with that dumb look,
君は悪い子なの？
are you a bad kid?
痛いのがお好き？ で、無残に
Do you like pain? And so mercilessly,
あら、お口はチャックで 何？何？
my, your lips are zipped, what? What?
声踊らされちゃう 君を喰う
Made to dance by your voice, I'll devour you.
What is...?
君の亡骸で 骨の髄まで
With your remains, to the marrow of your bones,
しゃぶり尽くせば もう空っぽのパペット
if I suck you dry, you're already an empty puppet.
胸が苦しいね 息が詰まるのね
Your chest hurts, doesn't it? You're suffocating, right?
それが恋と教えてあげる Ah-ha-ha
I'll teach you that's what love is, ah-ha-ha.
君はピエロね 愛を裂いて
You're a clown, tearing love apart.
人間の形した君はLove it
In human form, you're love it.
イカレちゃったのね 恋は盲目で
You've gone insane, love is blind.
死体にしてあげるわ 逝って Ah-ha-ha
I'll turn you into a corpse, pass on, ah-ha-ha.
報い 償え 汚れた血に溺れるまで
Suffer retribution, atone, until drowning in stained blood.
大体のトんで行け 息が止まるまで
Just fly away, until your breath stops.
報い 償え 汚れた血に溺れるまで
Suffer retribution, atone, until drowning in stained blood.
大体のトんで行け 息が止まるまで
Just fly away, until your breath stops.
皆さん、本日は...
Everyone, today...
猪崎リオナ 生誕祭2026に
to the Isaki Riona Birthday Festival 2026,
遊びに来てくれて、本当にありがとうございます！
thank you so very much for coming to hang out!
『Red the Showtime』、
"Red the Showtime,"
えー、『ビビッドビート』、『Loveit?』、
um, "Vivid Beat," "Loveit?,"
3曲続けて披露させていただきました！
I performed three songs in a row!
どうでしたか？
How was it?
改めて自己紹介をさせてください！
Allow me to introduce myself once again!
私の元においで、リオナインザステージ！
Come to my side, Riona in the Stage!
ぶろぐらのリーダー、猪崎リオナです！ぶらぶらー！
I'm the leader of BroGura, Isaki Riona! Bura-bura!
よろしくお願いします！
It's nice to meet you all!
はぁ、息切れが...息切れが酷いんですけど。
Haa, I'm out of breath... I'm terribly out of breath, but...
はい、今日のですね、ハッシュタグはこちら！
Yes, today's hashtag is this right here!
猪崎リオナ生誕祭2026です！
It's #IsakiRionaBirthdayFestival2026!
たくさん、たくさん呟いてください！
Please post lots and lots of tweets!
私絶対見に行くのでね、
I'll definitely go check them out,
みんなが感想とかを送ってくれるの、すごく楽しみにしています！
so I'm really looking forward to seeing everyone's thoughts and comments!
そしてですね、本日ライブパフォーマンスさせていただくステージはこちらです！
And also, the stage where I'm performing live today is this right here!
どうですか？
How do you like it?
ショーみたいでさ、めっちゃ良くない？
It's like a real show, isn't it super cool?
あとね、猪崎リオナっていう名前がたくさん刻まれていたり、
Also, the name "Isaki Riona" is engraved all over,
ハートの風船だったり、王冠だったり、
along with heart balloons and crowns...
色んな装飾があって、とてもキラキラしてます！
There are all kinds of decorations, making it so sparkly!
ここでね、踊れることが今日すごくすごく幸せです！
Being able to dance here today makes me so, so happy!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
そして、本日のライブのタイトルが『The One and Only』となっております。
And the title of today's live concert is "The One and Only."
こちらの意味は「唯一無二」という意味です。
This means "unique and peerless."
このタイトルに恥じないように、全力で、全力でパフォーマンスしていくので、
To live up to this title, I'll be performing with all my might, with everything I've got,
どうかこの時間が、
so that this time...
あなたの心に何か届けられる、そんな時間になれるように、
will be a time that delivers something special to your heart,
今日は頑張りたいと思います！
I'll do my very best today!
それでは次は、お待ちかねのゲストパートです！
And now, next up is the long-awaited guest part!
どうぞ！
Please enjoy!
Virtual Blah Blah Blah
I'm a B
I'm a B, La Vida
La Vida, Love
Love That Blah Blah Blah
たかがノーマルなこと 触らばカワイイのこと
It's just a normal thing; if you touch it, it's cute.
高天ヶ原から ほら 陽動していけ
From Takamagahara, look, launch a diversion.
Hi, そう メンヘラ でも面がキュートならメンキラー
Hi, yeah, menhera, but if your face is cute, you're a men-killer.
とか貼られた レッテル 逝ってる メンタルは
Or so the label says; as for this far-gone mentality...
最上 スマイルで 転がしてけ パンパン
roll them over with a top-notch smile, bang bang!
誤魔化してる 正真正銘 晒されたら バイバイ
Deceiving, genuine; once exposed, it's bye-bye.
なんてな
Just kidding!
I am a B I'm a B I'm a あわあわよ
I am a B, I'm a B, I'm all flustered!
I am a B だがディーバ 見たら罠よ
I am a B, but a diva; if you look, it's a trap!
夢見てる少年へ 夢見てる少女へ
To the dreaming boys, to the dreaming girls,
みんなラ・ヴィータ 甘々甘々甘々の
everyone, la vita, sweet, sweet, overly sweet,
刺激 ガリガリ もう消耗 我を忘んな 我を...
scratching sensation, already exhausted, don't lose yourself, don't lose...
センター 誰よりも客を寄せるパンダ
Center, a panda attracting customers more than anyone,
我は何だ まるで生んだ自己愛性勝者
what am I? Like a newborn narcissistic victor.
Am I V?
I'm a V　I'm a She
I'm a V, I'm a she,
A lie the lie　I'm a She
a lie, the lie, I'm a she.
空似に
Looking alike,
互いに So Love me
to each other, so love me.
お出ませモンスター
Here comes the monster.
Um, my name is blah blah
愛でられたら墓場までラフター
if I'm adored, I'll laugh all the way to the grave.
I'm a Vだ 舐めんなバッター
I'm a V, don't mess with me, batter,
心の中 Smooth like butter
deep inside, smooth like butter.
Touch me したいなら ほら￥だ
If you wanna touch me, look, it's yen,
Catch me でハイピース
catch me and give a high peace sign.
召し上がる主客わからないが Wow
Don't know who's host or guest eating, but wow,
我心叫ぶ一つも Lifer
my heart screams, not a single one is a lifer.
生きる姿や魂を今
My living form and soul right now,
二つにして愛をバラバラに
splitting them in two, tearing love apart.
生まれた時の喜びは
Is it really okay if the joy from when we were born
没収に さよならでいいの？
is confiscated with a goodbye?
ダメね
No way.
Wacha wacha
Wacha は めちゃめちゃ？
Is wacha all chaotic?
Wacha wacha
Wacha は めちゃめちゃ？
Is wacha all chaotic?
楽観なのかな アララ
Is it optimism? Oh dear,
五感で共感ね 解体な正体ね あら
empathy through five senses, a dismantled identity, oh my.
Wacha は めちゃめちゃ？
Is wacha all chaotic?
楽観なのかな アララ 五感で共感ね
Is it optimism? Oh dear, empathy through five senses,
一巻の終わりだね
it's the end of the story, isn't it?
Ah
I'm a V　I'm a V　I'm a あわあわよ
I'm a V, I'm a V, I'm bubbling over,
I'm a Vida　I am Diva　淫らは嫌やよ
I'm a Vida, I am Diva, I hate indecency.
夢見てる少年
To the dreaming boys,
夢見てる少女へ
to the dreaming girls,
Vなら Vidaは 甘甘甘甘なのだ (No!)
if it's V, vida is super sweet! (No!)
そうよ 幼少 言われたろんだ
That's right, we were told as kids,
あのヒーローショーの人形の背中にゃ
on the back of the costume at that hero show,
チャックは付いてないから 開くな！
there's no zipper, so don't open it!
バーチャルだ ヒューマンだ
It's virtual, it's human,
四の五の言うな 存在はワンワンダ
don't quibble, this existence is one-wonder.
泣いても 惚れても 死の五 バラバラな
Whether you weep or fall in love, scattered into pieces...
バーチャブラブラ
Virtual blah blah,
virtual blah blah.
ブラブラブラブラ！
Blah blah blah blah!
バーチャブラブラ
Virtual blah blah,
virtual blah blah.
Are you ready for...
惚れたら死ぬぞ
Fall in love and you'll die!
バーチャブラブラ
Virtual blah blah,
virtual blah blah.
バーチャブラブラ
Virtual blah blah,
virtual blah blah.
Um... I'm a V
空先輩ー！
Sora-senpai!
来てくれてありがとうございます！
Thank you so much for coming!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
一緒に踊れて嬉しかったです！
I was so happy to dance with you!
えへへ～
Ehehe~
そらりお～！
SoraRio~!
そらりおは不滅だよ～！
SoraRio is eternal~!
バイバーイ！
Bye-bye!
Yeah, that's karma. Yeah, get 'em.
How?
Checkmate, I'm a superstar. Stay insane, but you rock with it, ah.
Yeah, like 24/7 I'm a hot mess ya love-hate. Get less boring, oh my god!
ホームラン、バタバタ swing my shot. Ah.
Home run, flapping around, swing my shot. Ah.
Yeah, like a villainous villainess, bring home the jackpot.
勇者も悪役も変わらない
Whether you're a hero or a villain, there's no difference.
派手にブチかまそう (Yeah, yeah, yeah)
Let's make a flashy splash. (Yeah, yeah, yeah)
Life's just a tightrope, why not stop to fool around?
"Chaotic good" is peak right now, I can show ya how. (Yeah, yeah, yeah)
Don't get confused, we are not the same.
I'm a ruthless dame, no way no way. Way-ah, way-ah!
"Good vs. evil" is so overdone!
Let's all kick back and party, just leave it to moi!
What's what? Ah!
Loosen my lips, loosen my li-li-lips, yeah, ah, that's karma, tada!
Loosen my lips, I'm about to say some ish, get it. Yeah, that's karma, tada!
Sorry I'm just better, sorry we're go-getters.
Ain't my fault we're wicked, stunning, tricky, why you running? Uh-huh.
Bet 'cha think you're clever. (Yeah, yeah, yeah)
Whatever! (Yeah, yeah, yeah)
Wow! Talk about a "kumbaya"! (Yeah, yeah, yeah)
Hey yeah, チェンジですわ
Hey yeah, it's time for a change.
フルボッコンボっちゃって 欲望召し上がれ
Beat them to a pulp and feast on your desires.
アイ ハート ゲッダン ウィンク see yonara 最高ですわ
Eye, heart, get down, wink, "see you later," it's the best!
ボンバー ドメスティック
Bomber, domestic,
ボンバー ドラマチック
bomber, dramatic.
愛しき人々 この指とまれ
Beloved people, gather around!
ハードにハートは ハイになって弾けて
Hard to heart, getting high and bursting,
恥じらい捨てちゃえ 叫び踊り誇れ
throw away your shyness, shout, dance, and be proud.
激動的ショウタイム 酔いしれてちょうだい
This turbulent showtime, please savor it completely!
道化のパラダイス
A paradise of fools,
惹かれ合う感覚が 共鳴 共鳴 ah
the feeling of mutual attraction is resonance, resonance, ah.
"Good vs. evil, but I'm which one?"
Just...
...stuck here in the middle, that's not any fun
Wa-ah
Loosen my lips, loosen my li-li-lips, yeah, ah,
that's karma, ta-da-ha-ha-ha
Wa, wa-ah
Loosen my lips, I'm about to say some ish, get it, yeah,
that's karma, ta-da-ha-ha-ha
想像から創造
From imagination to creation,
衝動から盲目
blinded by impulse.
ほら あんたのように華麗に 反転変化にさえ
See, just like you, splendidly reversing even change,
ドクドク 支配欲 (ba-ya-ya-ya)
throbbing desire to control (ba-ya-ya-ya),
クライホリック (ba-ya-ya-ya)
Cryaholic (ba-ya-ya-ya).
Ah ドクドクくわえや (ba-ya-ya-ya)
Ah, throbbing and taking it in (ba-ya-ya-ya)!
Sorry, I'm just better
Sorry, we're go-getters
Ain't my fault we're wicked, stunning, tricky, why you running?
Bet'cha think you're clever (ba-ya-ya-ya)
Whatever! (ba-ya-ya-ya)
Ha, talk about a kumbaya
Isekai Queen switch チューニング マイナー
Isekai Queen, switch tuning minor,
カラフルに cacophony (ba-ya-ya-ya)
a colorful cacophony (ba-ya-ya-ya),
キスで優雅に はちゃめちゃ
elegantly chaotic with a kiss.
Welcome to Miss Fortune's Game
ba-ya-ya-ya
カリオペ先輩、来てくれてありがとうございます！
Calliope-senpai, thank you so much for coming!
イエーイ！楽しかったー！また歌いましょう！
Yay! That was so much fun! Let's sing together again!
はい！また歌いましょう！
Yes! Let's definitely sing again!
また歌いましょう！
Let's sing again!
歌いましょう！チュッチュッ
Let's sing! Chu chu!
じゃあじゃあ！
See ya!
カルテNo.2222
[Title: Karte No.2222]
あー…♡
Ah...♡
2-2-2- (Kyu Kyu)
2-2-2- (Doom Doom Doom)
2-2-2-2 (Kyu Kyu Kyu Kyuru)
2-2-2-2-2
2- (Kyu Kyu)
2- (Burn Burn)
Chu Chu Chu
OPEN YOUR KARTE♡
救助不可能 (Darling)
Impossible to rescue (Darling),
恋の病なの (Dirty)
it's lovesickness (Dirty).
どんどん熱を上げていく Virus (Love me)
A virus pushing my fever higher and higher (Love me).
危険な治療 (Twinkle)
A dangerous treatment (Twinkle),
試してみる？ (Blink)
wanna give it a try? (Blink)
悪魔で天使の優等生
Just an angelic honor student,
Heaven in hell
ドキ (ドキ) 動機は純粋
Pound (pound), my motives are pure,
(甘い) 曖昧乙女心
(sweet) an ambiguous maiden's heart.
どっち (どっち)
Which one? (Which one?)
さあ 手の平の迷宮へようこそ
Now then, welcome to the labyrinth in the palm of my hand.
「いい子だね♡」
"Such a good kid♡"
カルテNo. (らぶ♡)
Karte No. (Love♡)
運命の 2222
Destined 2222,
鳴り止まない (らぶ♡)
unceasing (Love♡),
サイレン音が Wee Woo Woo
the siren sound goes wee woo woo.
好き？好き？ 速まる 愛の心電図 (2-2)
Love me? Love me? An accelerating love ECG (2-2).
はい お薬をどうぞ♡
Here, take your medicine♡
To to to u♡
2-2-2- (Kyu Kyu Kyu Kyuru)
2-2-2-2 (Doom Doom Doom Doom)
2- (Kyu Kyu)
2- (Zoom)
2-2- (Kyu Kyu)
2-2-2- (Burn Burn Burn)
Chu Chu Chu
OPEN YOUR KARTE♡
二十四時間 (During)
Twenty-four hours (During),
呼吸困難 (Dizzy)
difficulty breathing (Dizzy).
真っ赤な薔薇のトゲにキスして (Kiss me)
Kiss the thorn of a crimson rose (Kiss me),
麻酔みたいな台詞 (Drinking)
lines like anesthesia (Drinking),
魔性の Babyface (Labyrinth)
a devilish babyface (Labyrinth).
籠で飛び交う青い鳥 (Try & Error)
Bluebirds flitting in a cage (Try & Error).
ドク (ドク) 毒みたいな
Thump (thump), like poison,
(Engulf) 笑顔に落下寸前
(Engulf) right on the verge of falling for that smile.
チク (タク)
Tick (tock),
もう時間がない 秘密の正体
there's no more time, the secret's true form.
「悪い子かも♡」
"I might be a bad kid♡"
カルテNo. (らぶ♡)
Karte No. (Love♡)
運命の 2222
Destined 2222,
追い付けない (らぶ♡)
can't catch up (Love♡),
超スピードで Wee Woo Woo Woo
at super speed, wee woo woo woo.
好き？好き？ 乱れる 愛の心電図 (2-2)
Love me? Love me? A scrambled love ECG (2-2).
もう重症みたいです…
It looks like a critical condition already...
Too too too too me♡
「先生、緊急事態です！」
"Doctor, we have an emergency!"
「カルテNo.2222の患者様です！」
"It's the patient from Karte No. 2222!"
「見てください！心電図がハートの形になってますー！」
"Look! The ECG is in the shape of a heart!"
「もしもーし、聞こえますか？どこか痛いところはありますか？」
"Hello? Can you hear me? Does it hurt anywhere?"
「えっ？可愛すぎて胸が苦しい？息ができない！？」
"Huh? You say we're so cute your chest hurts? You can't breathe?!"
「もっと好きになっちゃうお注射しましょうね♡」
"Let's give you a shot to make you fall in love even more♡"
「大丈夫ですよー、ずっと私が手を握っていますからね」
"It's okay~ I'll be holding your hand the whole time."
「心拍数がどんどんあがっていまーす！」
"The heart rate is rising fast!"
「わ！大変です！気を失っちゃったみたいですー」
"Whoa! Oh no! It looks like they fainted~"
「わたしの声聞こえますかー？」「好きなところ言えますかー？」
"Can you hear my voice~?" "Can you name what you love about us~?"
「もうこうなったらあの手しかない！」「あーあ、だから言ったのに♡」
"There's only one way left! Clear!" "Ah-ah, I told you so♡"
カルテNo. さあ選んで 4 Card
Karte No., come pick a 4 Card,
裏表ツインテールの Joker
the two-faced twintail Joker.
Time over …そう神様さえ言う通り
Time over, just as even God decrees,
You're falling Take over
…ぎゅっと結んだリボン
...A tightly tied ribbon,
誓いましょう ding dong
let's make a vow, ding dong.
運命の警告が連なる暗示
An omen of successive warnings of fate,
2! 2! 2!
カルテNo. (らぶ♡)
Karte No. (Love♡)
運命の 2222
Destined 2222,
鳴り止まない (らぶ♡)
unceasing (Love♡),
サイレン音が Wee Woo Woo Woo
the siren sound goes wee woo woo woo.
好き？好き？ 速まる 愛の心電図 (2-2)
Love me? Love me? An accelerating love ECG (2-2).
はい お薬をどうぞ♡
Here, take your medicine♡
To to to u♡
2-2-2- (Kyu Kyu Kyu Kyuru)
2- (Doom Doom Doom Doom)
2-2- (Kyu Kyu Kyu Kyuru)
2- (Zoom Zoom Zoom)
2-2-2-2 (Kyu Kyu Kyu Kyuru)
2- (Burn Burn Burn)
Chu Chu Chu
OPEN YOUR KARTE♡
見上げた あの夜空に
Up in that night sky I looked upon,
浮かぶ 星たち
the stars are floating.
ふっと 君の声が
Suddenly, I wonder if your voice
あの頃 輝いてたかな
was sparkling back in those days.
今になっては
Now that time has passed,
ずっと 分からないまま
I'll never know for sure.
オーケストラ
[Song: Orchestra]
あの時 君が付いた嘘
Back then, that lie you told—
問い正せずに 泣いたあの坂道
unable to question it, I cried on that sloped road.
この先 君と会えないの？
Will I never be able to see you again from now on?
離れ離れに 身を任せてた
I simply surrendered to our drifting apart.
いつもの後悔が 風に消えてく
My usual regrets fade away into the wind.
誰にも見せない その姿を
That side of you that you show to no one else...
もうちょっとだけ 見てたかったんだ
I just wanted to keep looking at it a little longer.
時がそっと 睨んでいる
Time is softly glaring down on us.
その手と手 繋いで
Holding hands with you,
笑いあった声 忘れはしないよ
the sound of our shared laughter, I will never forget.
こんなにも流してた涙も
All these tears that we shed,
語る声も オーケストラ
and our talking voices, become an orchestra.
やがて訪れたよね
Eventually, it came, didn't it?
さよならの声 忘れはしないよ
That voice saying goodbye, I will never forget.
あんなにも近くにいたはずが
We were supposed to be so close, but
今では繋がりなんて
now, the only thing connecting us
あの空だけ
is that distant sky.
夜空の交換をしよう
"Let's trade night skies,"
馬鹿らしくなって 投げた午前3時
feeling ridiculous, I threw in the towel at 3 AM.
この先 君と何年も
From now on, even if for years with you
時の流れに 身を任せても
I surrender myself to the passage of time...
いつものジョークが 街に消えてく
Our usual jokes fade away into the city.
誰にも見せない 僕の姿を
That side of myself that I show to no one else...
もうちょっとだけ 見せたかったんだ
I just wanted to show you a little more.
時がそっと 睨んでいる
Time is softly glaring down on us.
この目と目 合わせて
Looking right into each other's eyes,
はっきりしたい もうできないかな
I want to make things clear—is it too late now?
こんなにももどかしくて辛いのが
Something so frustrating and painful
音を立てる オーケストラ
makes up a roaring orchestra.
どこで何をしてるの？
Where and what are you doing?
分からないのは 僕のせいなんだね
Not knowing must all be my fault, isn't it?
永遠にこんな日が来るなんて
To think a day like this would last forever—
神様イタズラなら 呪いたいぐらい
if this is God's prank, I want to curse it.
その手と手 繋いで
Holding hands with you,
笑いあった声 忘れはしないよ
the sound of our shared laughter, I will never forget.
こんなにも流してた涙も
All these tears that we shed,
語る声も オーケストラ
and our talking voices, become an orchestra.
やがて訪れたよね
Eventually, it came, didn't it?
さよならの声 忘れ...
That voice saying goodbye, I will never...
暮れはしないよ
It will never fade.
あんなにも近くにいたはずが
We were supposed to be so close,
今では繋がりなんて
but now the only bond between us...
この空だけ
...is this sky.
Woah-oh-oh-oh...
せーの！
Ready, go!
リオナ、お誕生日おめでとう！
Riona, happy birthday!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
なんとFGのみんなが来てくれました！ありがとう！
Everyone from FG came to celebrate with me! Thank you!
イエーイ！／おめでとう！
Yay! / Happy Birthday!
ついにね、初めての生誕ライブで、そしてFGでこうやってライブできてすごく嬉しいよー！
It's finally my very first birthday live, and I'm so happy we could perform like this with FG!
呼んでくれてありがとう！
Thanks for inviting us!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
エモかったね／エモかった？／めっちゃエモかったね／ホント？
That was so emotional. / It was? / Super emotional! / Really?
え、どうですか？エモかったですかー？
What did you all think? Was it emotional?
泣いちゃったよ、リオナちゃん／泣いちゃった？
I ended up crying, Riona-chan. / You cried?
ちょっと泣いちゃった／嘘だよ／ホントに泣いてるかそれ？
I cried a little. / That's a lie. / Are you actually crying?
みんなとこうやってね、まあみんなの誕生日ライブがあるかどうか、まあ分かんないんだけどー…
Being here together... Well, I don't know if the rest of you will get birthday lives, but...
どうだろうな／え、リオナだけやって2期生たちは無いの？／やだやだ！
I wonder. / Wait, only Riona gets one and the 2nd gen doesn't? / No way!
うち等もさせてよ！／どうなのー？／まあ、リオナ次第ですね／裏で交渉するか
Let us do one too! / What do you think? / Well, it's up to Riona. / Let's negotiate backstage.
リーダー、出させてくれてありがとうございます！／出させてもらって／ありがとうございます
Leader, thank you so much for letting us perform! / Thanks for having us! / Thank you!
まあ、まあ、それはやっぱり置いときまして、
Well, well, let's put that aside for now.
今日は誕生日プレゼントにみんなからの、超絶可愛い「おめでと、リオナおめでとー」っていうプレゼントが欲しいんだけどいいかな？
Today, for my birthday gift, I'd like a super cute "Congrats, congrats Riona!" from everyone. Would that be okay?
嫌です／嫌です／誕生日なのに！？／誕生日おめでとうございます
No thanks. / No way. / But it's my birthday?! / Happy birthday.
もらっていいですか、プレゼント？／じゃあ、おめでとー！
Can I have my present? / Alright, congrats!
ありがとうね／「おめでとー」みたいなやつ
Thank you. / Like a cute "Congrats!" kind of thing.
じゃあ「せーの」って言うから、「リオナおめでとう」って言ってね。プレゼントね、プレゼント。
Okay, so I'll say "Ready, go," then say "Congrats Riona," okay? As my present!
ま、プレゼントならしゃあないな／ちゃんと可愛くやれよ
Well, if it's a present, guess we have to. / Make sure you do it cutely!
可愛くだからね／可愛くね／そうだよ、ちゃんと可愛くだよ
Cutely, alright? / Yeah, cute! / That's right, make it super cute.
まあまあ任せろって／オッケー、分かった／可愛くね／行くよ？
Come on, leave it to us. / Alright, got it. / Cute, okay? / Here we go!
せーの！
Ready, go!
リオナ、おめ…／おい、待て待て！／バラバラ、バラバラ！
Riona, con— / Hey, wait, wait! / Totally out of sync!
全然揃ってない／もう全然ダメー！
That wasn't in sync at all! / Totally useless!
でも、ちょっとじゃあ見本見せてよ／見本見せてよ
But hey, why don't you show us an example? / Show us how it's done!
初めての生誕ライブ…／そうだよ、リオナさんにね、愛の言葉みたいなの
It's my first birthday live... / Exactly, give us some words of love for Riona-san.
愛がいいよね／愛がいい／愛の言葉
Love is good. / Yeah, love! / Words of love.
セクシーで可愛くて愛／セクシー、可愛い、愛
Sexy, cute, and loving. / Sexy, cute, loving.
じゃあ全身で／いきますよ／愛の言葉まで
Alright, with your whole body! / Here goes! / Give us your loving words!
3、2、1、はい！
3, 2, 1, go!
今年も来年も再来年も、あなたに祝ってもらえますように！
May you celebrate with me this year, next year, and the year after that!
きゃー！／かわいい！／ありがとうー！
Kyaa! / So cute! / Thank you!
あなたはまだお残りです／残る
You are staying behind. / Staying.
うーん…
Mmm...
まるでこの世界で 二人だけみたいだね
It feels as if we're the only two people in this world.
なんて少しだけ 夢を見てしまっただけ
I was only dreaming, just for a little while.
爪先に月明かり 花束の香りに 指に触れる夜
Moonlight on my toes, the scent of a bouquet, on this night our fingers touch.
さよなら もう行かなきゃ 何もかも忘れて
Goodbye, I have to go now, forgetting everything.
硝子の上を 裸足のまま歩く
Walking barefoot on shattered glass,
痛むごとに 血が流れて落ちていく
with every ache, blood flows and drips down.
お願い その赤い足跡を辿って
Please, follow those crimson footprints...
会いに来て
...and come see me.
錆びたプールに放たれてく金魚
Goldfish released into a rusted pool,
骨壺のなか 隠した林檎
an apple hidden inside an urn,
しなびた首の肌に残る傷跡
the scars remaining on withered neck skin...
水のように泳いだ迷子
A lost child swimming like water,
ここにいるよ
I'm right here.
何もしず ずっと見てるよ
Doing nothing, just watching over you.
今夜 間違い見出そう
Tonight, let's find what went wrong.
そばにいてよ
Stay by my side,
遊びに行こうよ
let's go out and play.
どこ 見るの
Where are you looking?
ガラスの上を 裸足のまま歩く
Walking barefoot over broken glass,
痛む毎に 血が流れて落ちてく
with every sting of pain, blood drips and falls.
お願い その赤い足跡を辿って
Please, follow these red footprints
会いに来て
and come see me.
まるで この世界で
As if in this whole world,
二人だけみたいだね
it's just the two of us.
なんて 少しだけ
...Or so I thought, for just a moment,
夢を見てしまっただけ
I was merely dreaming.
Ah...
Ah... La la la...
Mmm...
頬を刺す 朝の山手通り
The morning Yamate Street stings my cheeks,
煙草の空き箱を捨てる
as I toss away an empty pack of cigarettes.
今日もまた 足の踏み場は無い
Today again, there's nowhere to even set foot,
小部屋が孤独を甘やかす
in this tiny room that indulges my loneliness.
不穏な悲鳴を愛さないで
"Don't love my restless shrieks,
未来等見ないで
don't look to the future.
確信出来る現在だけ重ねて
Just pile up this certain present,
あたしの名前をちゃんと呼んで
properly call my name,
身体を触って 必要なのは 是だけ認めて
touch my body, and acknowledge that this is all I need."
Ah...
Ah... ah...
愛してる 独り泣き叫んで
Bawling all alone, "I love you,"
夜道を弄れど虚しい
I fumble down the night road, but it's all in vain.
改札の安蛍光灯は
The ticket gate's cheap fluorescent lights
貴方の影すら落とさない
don't even cast your shadow.
歪んだ無常の遠き日も
Even those warped, fleeting, distant days
セヴンスターの香り
carry the scent of Seven Stars,
味わう如く 季節を呼び起こす
evoking the seasons as if savoring them.
あたしが望んだこと自体 矛盾を優に超えて
The very fact that I wished for anything easily surpassed all contradiction,
一番愛しいあなたの声迄 掠れさせて居たのだろう
and it must have made even your dearest voice grow hoarse.
Ah...
静寂を
The silence...
…破る ドイツ車と パトカー
...Breaking through, German cars and police cruisers,
あぁ サイレン 爆音
Ah, sirens and roaring engines,
現実界 或る 浮遊
A certain floating feeling in the real world.
「不穏な悲鳴を愛さないで
"Don't love my ominous screams,
未来等 見ないで
Don't look to the future.
確信出来る
Just hold onto
現在(いま)だけ重ねて
the present you can be sure of.
あたしの名前をちゃんと呼んで
Say my name properly,
身体を触って
touch my body.
必要なのは
All I need is this,
是だけ 認めて」
just acknowledge me."
「不穏な悲鳴を愛さないで
"Don't love my ominous screams,
確信出来る
Just hold onto
現在(いま)だけ重ねて
the present you can be sure of.
あたしの名前をちゃんと呼んで
Say my name properly,
身体を触って
touch my body.
必要なのは
All I need is this,
是だけ 認めて」
just acknowledge me."
頬を刺す 朝の山手通り
Morning on Yamate Street stings my cheeks,
煙草の空き箱を捨てる
I throw away an empty cigarette pack.
今日もまた 足の踏み場は無い
Today again, there's nowhere to even step,
小部屋が孤独を甘やかす
this small room indulges my loneliness.
La la la la la...
Ah-ha... ah-ha...
ねえ あんた解っちゃ居ない
Hey, you really don't understand.
誰彼それもお手元の世界に夢中
Everyone's obsessed with the world in their hands,
化け物の飼い方を学んでる
learning how to raise a monster.
選ばれる為なら舌を売る
They'd sell their tongue just to get chosen,
裏切られた分だけ墓を掘る
digging graves for every betrayal.
脳足りんのおつむがどうかして
With their brainless heads going crazy,
うすら寒い言葉ばかりになる
it's nothing but chilling, empty words.
覚えない顔とバイバイできるなら
If I can say bye-bye to unmemorable faces,
阿修羅にだってなれるわ
I could even become an Ashura.
逃げるエスケープ エスケープ エスケープ 仏のまま
Running away, escape, escape, escape, like a Buddha,
飛べるステップ ステップ ステップ 仰せのまま
flying, step, step, step, as you command.
アンダスタン アンダスタン
Understand? Understand?
堂々 閻魔様さえ喰らって
Proudly devouring even King Enma,
騙るスニーク スニーク スニーク 嵐の中
deceiving, sneak, sneak, sneak through the storm,
跳ねるスキップ スキップ スキップ あそへの河原
prancing, skip, skip, skip by that riverbed.
アンダスタン アンダスタン
Understand? Understand?
いっそ骨の髄までしゃぶって
Might as well suck them dry to the bone.
ねえ あんた解っちゃ居ない
Hey, you really don't understand.
日々の染みを木々にくべて暖を取り合う
Burning daily stains as firewood to share warmth,
義理を敷いた彼の肢体は散り散りになる
his limbs, bound by duty, are torn to pieces.
知りもせずに意味を美意識だと崇める
Worshiping meaning as aesthetics without understanding,
擬似餌染みた恣意に御の字だった
satisfied with arbitrary whims resembling fake bait.
愉快なご託のフルコースに
To this full-course meal of amusing nonsense,
うわべのツラして可愛がった
I showed shallow affection with a fake face.
下らない僧と踊るくらいなら
Rather than dancing with a worthless monk,
悪魔と手繋ぐわ
I'd rather hold hands with the devil.
逃げるエスケープ エスケープ エスケープ 仏のまま
Running away, escape, escape, escape, like a Buddha,
飛べるステップ ステップ ステップ 仰せのまま
flying, step, step, step, as you command.
アンダスタン アンダスタン
Understand? Understand?
阿鼻地獄の果てまでロックオン
Locked on all the way to the depths of Avici Hell,
騙るスニーク スニーク スニーク 嵐の中
deceiving, sneak, sneak, sneak through the storm,
跳ねるスキップ スキップ スキップ あそへの河原
prancing, skip, skip, skip by that riverbed.
アンダスタン アンダスタン
Understand? Understand?
あんた寝言はあの世で言って
Save your sleep talk for the afterlife.
逃げるエスケープ エスケープ エスケープ 仏のまま
Running away, escape, escape, escape, like a Buddha,
飛べるステップ ステップ ステップ 仰せのまま
flying, step, step, step, as you command.
アンダスタン アンダスタン
Understand? Understand?
堂々 閻魔様さえ喰らって
Proudly devouring even King Enma,
騙るスニーク スニーク スニーク 嵐の中
deceiving, sneak, sneak, sneak through the storm,
跳ねるスキップ スキップ スキップ あそへの河原
prancing, skip, skip, skip by that riverbed.
アンダスタン アンダスタン
Understand? Understand?
いっそ骨の髄までしゃぶって
Might as well suck them dry to the bone.
ねえ ぎゃあぎゃあ言っちゃって…
Hey, squawking so loudly...
ああ、頭を垂れないで
Ah, don't hang your head down!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
みんなありがとう！
Thank you, everyone!
やばい、ちょっと息が…
Oh boy, I'm a bit out of breath...
お水飲ませてくださいね。すみませんね。
Let me drink some water. Excuse me for a sec.
はぁ、美味い！
Ah, delicious!
いつもありがとうございます。
Thank you as always.
お待たせしてすみませんね。
Sorry to keep you waiting.
えっと、先ほどは
Um, earlier,
『ジェヘナ』と『罪と罰』と
we had "Gehenna," "Crime and Punishment,"
『阿修羅ちゃん』をお届けしました！
and "Ashura-chan"!
どうでしたでしょうか？
How did you like them?
この後もまだまだライブは続きます！
The live show will keep going after this!
まだ披露してないあんな曲や
There might be that song I haven't shown yet,
こんな曲があるかもね！
or even this song!
なので、チャンネルはそのまま、
So stay tuned to this channel,
まだ見ててくれたら嬉しいです！
and keep watching—I'd be so happy!
ここでみんなにお知らせをさせてください！
Now, please let me make an announcement to everyone!
こちらです！
Here it is!
伊咲リオナ誕生日記念2026のグッズが出ます！
Merchandise for Isaki Riona Birthday Celebration 2026 is coming out!
やったー！
Yay!
では、詳細を見ていきましょう！
Now, let's take a look at the details!
まずはこちらです！
First up is this!
「RIONA ON THE ステージタペストリー」！
The "Riona On The Stage Tapestry"!
イラストは今回、みんちゅう先生にご依頼させていただきました！
For the illustration, we commissioned Minchuu-sensei!
ライブ中のリオナをテーマに描かれたイラストで、
It's an illustration themed around Riona performing live,
とっても可愛いイラストになってるので、
and it turned out super cute,
タペストリーでぜひ堪能してください！
so please enjoy it on the tapestry!
2つ目は、こちら！
The second item is this!
「リオナとおそろいネックレス」！
The "Matching Necklace with Riona"!
真ん中には王冠のデザイン、
In the center is a crown design,
周りには伊咲リオナのロゴが入っていますので、
and around it is Isaki Riona's logo,
あの、シンプルになってますのでね、
so it has a simple design,
ぜひリオナとおそろいにしてくれたら嬉しいです！
and I'd love it if you wore it to match with Riona!
次は、こちら！
Next is this!
「リオナのぬいを 入れるポーチ」！
The "Pouch to Put Riona's Plushie In"!
リオナっぽさ全開のぬいポーチになってます！
It's a plushie pouch packed with Riona vibes!
ぜひ、ま、リオナをね、ま、リオナのぬいを
Please put, well, Riona—well, Riona's plushie—
入れてくれたら嬉しいなと思います！
inside, and I'd be so happy!
ぬい以外に使っても大丈夫だよーポーチになるよ。
It can also be used as a pouch for things other than plushies!
そしてそして、最後は、こちら！
And next, last but not least, here it is!
「くしゃみ連発ぬいキーホルダー」！
The "Rapid Sneezing Plushie Keychain"!
今回、描き下ろしイラストの衣装の
It's a plushie keychain wearing the outfit
ぬいぐるみキーホルダーになってます！
from the newly drawn illustration!
なんとね、この手の部分をね、
And when you press its hand,
ポチッて押すと「はっくしょん！」って言うので、
it goes "Achoo!",
あの、いっぱい押してね、いっぱい浴びてもらえればと
so please press it a lot and get showered in sneezes,
思います！
I hope!
そして改めてね、フルセットの方を全部見ていきましょう！
Now, let's take a look at the full set all together!
こちら！
Here!
盛りだくさん！
So much stuff!
もちろん、フルセット購入特典もあります！
Of course, there are also full-set purchase bonuses!
こちら！
Here they are!
フルセット購入特典の1つ目は、
The first full-set purchase bonus is
直筆サインと箔押しメッセージ入りの
a backstage pass-style card with an authentic
バックステージ風、違う、
handwritten signature and foil-stamped message—wait, no,
バックステージパス風カードです！
a backstage pass-style card!
こちらも、みんちゅう先生のイラストに、
This also features Minchuu-sensei's illustration,
全て私がね、1つ1つ、
and I will personally, one by one,
ほんののののって、サインさせていただくので、
sign every single one,
よかったらぜひ買ってみてください！
so please be sure to grab one if you'd like!
2つ目は、特典ボイス！
The second is a bonus voice!
「ライブ前に君と」です！
It's titled "With You Before the Live"!
ライブ前にね、こう緊張してね、
It's a situation where Riona is nervous before the live,
うぇぇんってなってるリオナを
going "Waaaah!",
励ますシチュエーションとなっております。
and you encourage her.
ぜひね、ボイスの方も聞いてくれると嬉しいです！
Please give the voice track a listen too, I'd be so happy!
こちらのグッズは、21時、9時からカートオープンです！
These goods will be available to order starting at 21:00, 9 PM!
みんなよかったらぜひぜひぜひゲットしてください！
Everyone, please definitely be sure to get them!
そして、大事なお知らせが、
And we have a second
2つ目、あります！
important announcement!
聞いてください！
Listen up!
ドロロロロロロ…ジャン！
Drumroll... Ta-da!
伊咲リオナの、
Isaki Riona's...
初ソロの新曲が出まーーす！
first solo original song is coming ouuuut!
やったーー！
Yay!
タイトルは『Ring my name』です！
The title is "Ring my name"!
こちら、私の思いだったり、
This song expresses my feelings,
これから先どうやってこう進んでいくか、
and how I will continue moving forward,
「私は進んでいくぞ！」というのが、
with "I'm going to forge ahead!"
オシャレで、優雅に、
being expressed in a stylish, elegant,
エレガントに表現された曲となっております！
and graceful way!
こちらセクシーな振り付けもついているので、
It also has sexy choreography,
よかったらそこに注目もしてくださると嬉しいです！
so I'd love it if you paid attention to that too!
この後、このライブが終わった後すぐに
Right after this live stream ends,
MVも公開されますし、
the MV will also premiere,
この後24時からデジタルリリースもあるので、
and it will be released digitally at midnight (24:00),
ぜひ、いっぱい聴いてくれると嬉しいです！
so please listen to it a lot, I'd be so happy!
やっぱり、この後は新曲やっちゃいますよね！
After all, we've gotta perform the new song next, right?!
ということでね、
So with that said,
まあやっていくんですけど、まあその前にね、ちょっと
we'll get to it, but before that,
語らせてくださいよ！
let me share a few thoughts with you!
まあね、リオナはね、
Well, Riona...
まだまだのことがいっぱいあって、
still has so much room to grow,
叶えたい夢もいっぱいあります！
and so many dreams I want to make come true!
なので、まだ何も手にしてない私かもしれませんが、
So, I might not have achieved much yet,
一緒についてきてくれたあなたと一緒に、
but together with you who have walked alongside me,
いろんな夢だったり思い出を作っていきたいです！
I want to create various dreams and memories!
絶対後悔はさせないので、
I promise I will never make you regret it,
これからも私についてきてくれると嬉しいです！
so I'd be so happy if you continue following me!
よろしくお願いします！
Thank you for your support!
そして、この後は、新曲の披露の前に、
And next, before performing the new song,
ホロライブの先輩方のオリ曲を使った
featuring original songs from my Hololive senpais,
ダンスメドレーをお届けします！
we'll bring you a dance medley!
こちらたくさんのジャンルのダンスを踊る…
Here, I'll be dancing many genres of dance...
ので 是非見てください！
So please be sure to watch!
行くよ、心の準備できた？
Here we go, are you ready?
ミュージック スタート！
Music, start!
Another killer track, yet another hit
Murder is so fucking kawaii
Murder is so fucking cute
かわいいね！
So cute!
死神って言えど Can't lie, I feel
Even as a Grim Reaper, can't lie, I feel...
Stepping outside, look at that sunshine
Who would've thought that this could happen to a Reaper, huh?
Kinda forgot the feeling of the outside, but it's alright
Gotta get up, start living this shit, gonna dance anyway 'cause it's human nature
一緒に楽しもう！
Let's enjoy this together!
Everybody in the place!
Doggy god's street
[Medley: Doggy god's street]
シャルイース
[Medley: Challece]
Get back, get back, yeah, get back, get back
奪っていいで、ビビディ・バ
Steal it away, Bibbidi-Ba
Riona in the house
I'm dressed in lace 甘い嘘は act
I'm dressed in lace, sweet lies are just an act
囁くの「Want more?」 吐息まで danger
Whispering, "Want more?" Even my breath is danger
Every step I take 心ごと奪って
Every step I take, stealing your whole heart
Velvet shadows call my name 微熱は隠して
Velvet shadows call my name, hiding the slight fever
午前零時 今、Veilが解け
At midnight, the veil now comes undone
I'm breaking into the night まだ夜は醒めやしない
I'm breaking into the night, the night won't awaken yet
さあ、誰も彼も焦がれるままで
Now then, let everyone yearn on
「私を見て。」
"Look at me."
Ring my name 響かせるわ 今から watch me rise
Ring my name, I'll make it resonate, now watch me rise
Bloom it now 咲き誇れば 煌めく reina
Bloom it now, when in full bloom, a glittering reina
指先まで優雅に揺れる 鏡越しの操り人形
Swaying gracefully to the fingertips, a marionette through the mirror
壊れそうに微笑んで
Smiling as if about to break
瞳の奥 falling low 唇まで like a ghost
Deep in my eyes falling low, even my lips like a ghost
I can't stop 巡る走馬灯 さあ、魅せましょう
I can't stop, a revolving lantern of memories; now, let me show you
「堕ちるまで」
"Until you fall"
綺麗な嘘で着飾らない no masquerade
Not dressing up in pretty lies, no masquerade
Go ahead, skip all cheap romance それならばいっそ Shall we dance?
Go ahead, skip all cheap romance; if so, shall we dance?
Come say reina! reina! reina!
It's showtime! Flavor, fly, no chaser
今さら、Bad, マーク、連打、Bot、ばっかやってられねーなー (笑)
Doing nothing but spamming dislikes and bots now, can't be bothered (lol)
I'm a wonder, can't look away, boy
魅せつけるの 全てを賭けて
I'll captivate you, staking everything
Are you ready?
Click, click, tap, tap, and keep on posing
Flick, flick, snap, snap, and everybody dancing
微熱の中
Amidst the slight fever,
景色が溶けて
the scenery melts away,
まだ夢は醒めない
and I have yet to wake from the dream.
To younger me, “you're alright”
To younger me, "you're alright."
名もなき あの頃に
To those days back when I was nameless,
「後悔はない」
"I have no regrets."
Ring my name 響かせるわ
Ring my name, I'll make it resonate!
今から watch me light
From now on, watch me light!
Bloom it now 咲き誇れば
Bloom it now, when I'm in full bloom,
煌めく Reina Ah
I'll be the sparkling Reina, ah!
明け方まで気高く踊る
Dancing nobly until dawn,
琥珀色のマスカレイド
an amber masquerade.
壊れそうに舞い乱れ
Dancing wildly as if about to shatter,
Viva la reina Cantad albaria
Ring my name 響かせるわ
Ring my name, I'll make it resonate!
今から watch me light
From now on, watch me light!
泡沫のティアラに魅せられ
Captivated by a transient tiara,
ただ憧れ
simply yearning for it,
手を伸ばして
reaching out my hand!
これからも私についてきてください！
Please keep following me from here on out!
以上、響咲リオナでした！
That was all from Hibiki Riona!
ありがとうございました！
Thank you so much!
響咲リオナ生誕祭2026
お越しいただき、ありがとうございました！！
[Hibiki Riona Birthday Festival 2026
Thank you so much for coming!!]
これからも皆さんとずっと一緒に居たい
貴方の居場所でありたいです！！
[I want to stay with everyone forever,
and be a place where you belong!!]
お届けしたパフォーマンスが貴方の心に
少しでも何かを残せているといいな
[I hope the performance I delivered today
leaves something special in your heart.]
本当に本当にありがとう！！
響咲リオナ
[Thank you so, so much!!
— Hibiki Riona]